nextadvisor.com 2019-07-17

# Privacy Policy - NextAdvisor

Next Advisor respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personal information you may provide us through our website.

This privacy policy explains what information may be collected on our website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties.

We urge you to read this privacy policy so that you understand our commitment to you and your privacy, and how you can contribute to that commitment.

### Information We Collect and How We Use It

We collect personal information from you when you fill out a form on our site. This includes, but is not limited to, your name and email address. You may also provide personal information via user reviews, blog comments or other information submitted through our website. We use this information to improve our service to you, provide you with updates, or to respond to your requests.

Whether or not you provide this information is your choice; however, in many instances this type of information is required to participate in the particular activity, realize a benefit we may offer, or gain access to certain content on our website.

### Information Collected Automatically

We may also collect technical information about you when you visit our website, which your web browser automatically sends whenever you visit a website on the internet. While this information does not identify a specific individual, it could be used to indirectly identify you. Our servers automatically record this information, which may include your IP address, browser type, browser language and other information about your web browser, type of device (including mobile device) used to access our website, and the date and time of your request. Gathering your information helps us ensure our website and other services work correctly and support our customer analytic efforts.

By visiting our website or using any of our services, you consent to our collection, use, disclosure, transfer and storage of information relating to you as set forth in this policy.

### Other Uses of Your Information

In addition to the uses described above, we also use your personal information to support our business functions, such as fraud prevention, marketing, and legal functions. To do this, we combine personal and non-personal information, collected online and offline, including information from third party sources.

### Links to Other sites

Next Advisor has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new website.

### Data Retention

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

### Use of Cookies

We may collect information about your use of our website through cookies and similar technology. A “cookie” is a small file we transfer to your computer, so we can keep track of your interests and/or preferences and recognize you as a return visitor. For example, we may use these technologies to collect information about ways visitors use our website, track users’ movements around the website (session replay), to support the features and functionality of our website, and to personalize your experience when you use our website.

If you don’t want us to use cookies when you use our website, you will need to change your internet browser settings so that your browser does not accept them. For more information about cookies, visit the help page for your web browser or see [https://www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/). Please note that if you disable your web browser’s cookies and other technologies, certain features of our website and services will be disabled and you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our site.

This website also uses a tool called Google Analytics to collect information about your use of this site. The tool uses cookies to collect standard internet log and visitor behavior information. This information is used to optimize the functionality of our site and serve ads to you based on your past visits. You may opt-out of Google Analytics cookies by visiting [this link](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

### Disclosure to Third Parties

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make sure a request, please contact us at the email or mailing address shown at the end of this policy.

### Collection of Information from Children

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy and safety of children, our website and services are directed towards a general audience and are not directed towards children. We do not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13 or minors otherwise defined in local law or regulation without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that someone under 13 has provided personal information through one of our websites, we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our databases.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may review and update this privacy policy periodically without any prior notice. We will post a notice to our website to inform you of any material changes to our privacy policy and indicate when it was most recently updated. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Next Advisor  
1423 Red Ventures Drive  
Fort Mill, SC 29707  
United States

Email: contact@nextadvisor.com

Last Reviewed: April 16, 2019
